iamnocturnal.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy | Positive Affirmation Domain Names

Positive Affirmation Domains, LLC dba IAmPowerful.com is committed to respecting the privacy and rights of our customers and all visitors to our web site. We take this matter very seriously, and have instituted many policies and procedures to ensure that none of your privacy rights are ever violated. Your information stays with us, will never be sold and is only used to better serve you in the future.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, or fill out a form.  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To personalize your experience**  
Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
  * **To improve our website**  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you
  * To improve customer service  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs
  * **To process transactions**  
Your information will be used to deliver the domain name you purchased. Your information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To send periodic emails**  
The email address you provide for order processing will be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.
  * **Unsubscribe**  
If at any time you wish to have your email address removed from our database please complete our Contact Web Form and mark “Unsubscribe” in the subject line and we will remove your name from our distribution list.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway provider’s database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your payment information will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. You can set your computer’s preferences to warn you each time a cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all cookies in your browser settings. If you choose to turn off your cookies, some of our website features may not function correctly. If this is the case you are always welcome to contact our Customer Service Department.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.

We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.

Please note that upon purchase of your domain name your information will be provided to the current registrar of record to allow you access and control of your domain name. Domain name registration contact information is made public through “whois” services and may be made public as required by the domain name registrar who maintains the domain registration.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online Privacy Policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Questions?

Should you have questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us via our Contact Web Form.
